ABOUT
GET INVOLVED
NEWS
DONATE

Mosaic teaches people — from 4th graders to adults in the workplace — how to reach over the things that divide usin order to build inclusive communities where we celebrate our diversity. In doing so, we transform our lives and our world. We make peace. Join us. 

ASSERTIVENESS
“I’ve changed after Mosaic because I’m better at solving conflicts and problems that the world has. Also, I’m better at standing up for myself. I used to be really passive. I think I’ll keep those changes.”— Tiana, Student

CONFLICT RESOLUTION
“I used to be a bystander, but now, after Mosaic, I know how to be an ally and help both the teaser and the person being teased.”— Jack, student

EMPATHY
“I learned how awful it feels to not be listened to, to be excluded and discriminated against.These things will be taken with me as I step out of Mosaic and into my school.”— Leah, student

TEAM BUILDING
“I saw some of my students rake on leadership roles in group activities, putting in to practice the wordsthey’ve used before — REALLY listening, opening up to new ideas, being allies, supporting each other.”— Leslie, teacher

PROGRAMS FOR STUDENTS
WORKPLACE TRAININGS

(across bottom)
The Mosaic Project | 580 Grand Avenue, Suite 303 | Oakland, CA 94610 | Ph:510-452-3377 | info@mosaicproject.org
